Are you hungry? Want some of this?
What a cutie! Do you want a snack?
Don't feed it junk.
Maybe I have leftovers from lunch...
Well, well. Back again, are we?
Here, doggie! For you!
Good boy!
Oh wow. This doggie has a big fat belly.
Plus-Sized Elf
The Baron's Dog and the Floating Pig
Sure enough!
Jogging is the best exercise for an elf!
Can't say the same for those losers...
Jeepers! I'm gonna shrivel up!
I can't take any more of this.
I'm wilting...
Twitch Twitch
BAAAARF
I invited them to join me,
but they all went home early!
Well, too much exertion can lead to injury.
By the way, do you come to
this park often, Elfuda?
Are you kidding?
Alternate Dimension
Entrance
This is where I crossed over into your world.
Huh?!
So, this is the gate to your world?
Yep. It's how I come and go.
Hold on. Does that mean
I could visit your world, too?
Only if you have mana.
Oh...
Alright. Let's get back to running!
Sure. I'm right behind you!
Whew, I'm beat. Time for a post-run snack.
SHAZAM!
Where the heck were you keeping that?!
What's the deal?
I'm betting it wants your fry.
But jeez! This doggie sure is big!
Seems a little fat if you ask me.
When it comes to animals:
the rounder, the cuter!
Who's a good doggie?
Aren't you just the cutest fluffball!
I always wanted to have a pet dog
when I was little.
Hey, come back!
Time for more pets!
Not the kinda guy who should keep a pet...
There, there! Good doggie!
Cut it out!
Look, Elfuda!
This dog turned into a person!
That's a lycanthrope.
Otherwise known as a werewolf.
They're prideful creatures that stand at
the top of the food chain.
But most of them have moody personalities
that are annoying to deal with.
Oh, shut up!
I'm not taking that from an elf
who reeks of grease!
I do NOT reek!
Elves have a floral aroma!
Don't take it personally.
Dogs just have a sharp nose.
I'm not a dog!
Why don't you just get lost!
I'm trying to exercise here!
Exercise?
I recognize the roundness of those curves...
You're on a diet, aren'tcha? Fatty fido!
I'm a wolf!
Humans bring me lots of yummy treats.
And I don't want to let any go to waste.
But eating all of them made me FAT!
Fucking humans!
What a dirty mouth...
I keep running my ass off,
but haven't shed any pounds!
And my body is so heavy
that it drags me down!
Then why not do some stretches
to help keep you moving?
Stretches?
Even just stretching for 5 minutes will have
a significant impact if you do it daily.
There are a lot of muscles clustered
near your hip joints in particular,
so loosen them up and get your
lymphatic system moving!
Man! Stretches really work!
My body feels nice and warm now.
You're pretty amazing for a mere human.
I'll give you permission to join my pack!
Pack?
Yeah, I'm the boss!
She really has a thing for you.
Lycanthropes typically operate in packs
only with their own kind.
It's rare for them to include an outsider.
Maybe you should learn to "shake."
Then she'll like you even more.
"Shake?" That's only for dogs...
Ah! D-don't get the wrong idea!
Shake.
Sit.
I dunno why, but I can't control myself!
You know, these guys can't disobey orders
from those who are higher up in the pack.
I'm betting she subconsciously
regarded you as superior while you
were instructing us on stretches.
Now she'll do whatever you want.
Even "beg" if you say the word.
"Beg"? Get serious...
Begging?! Absolutely not!
Uh, I'm sorry!
Oh no! I can't stop! Please no!
I'm gonna beg!
She reverted to her original form.
The overwhelming shame made it
impossible to stay as a human, I guess.
Wah! I only wanted to lose some weight!
I'm really sorry about this!
What kind of pathetic pooch
cries over a little begging?
Excuse you!
Come on, Elfuda. Don't be so mean.
Nobody gets away with making fun of me!
You've got guts to fight with an elf.
All right. Let me teach you some manners.
Sniffle
Plus-Sized Elf
Plus-Sized Elf!
Let's move on from jogging.
It's time to try the exercise
that's most helpful for dieting.
One, two, three, four!
Five, six, seven, eight!
Chlorine ain't good fer me...
Oopsies. I sucked up too much water...
Tremble
Aw, jeez. Guess I gotta haul
you guys to the rest area.
Hup! Heave-ho!
Hey! Be more gentle!
I'm a wolf, but I can swim like a fish!
Just watch!
See?
So slow...
Hey, human. We're done warming up.
So, why'd you recommend we try swimming?
He just wanted to see us
wearing swimsuits, duh.
No!
Swimming is the perfect exercise
when you're on a diet.
It takes a lot of energy to move
when you're underwater.
And the water resistance helps to evenly
stimulate all the muscles in your body.
Plus, the buoyancy reduces
the strain put on your joints,
which means less injuries!
Makes sense! I'll give it a shot!
You should have told me
that you don't know how to swim!
Fortunately, water walking has
just as many benefits.
Make sure to move your whole body!
And after 30 minutes or so...
Huh?
Oh, hey! Boss!
What a coincidence!
You came for a swim, too, boss?
Pardon me, but I think you're confused.
I'm not this "Boss" person.
My name is Oku.
Huh?
Oops. I guess she does look
a bit larger than the boss is...
Shucks! You look just like her.
I'm so sorry.
That's all right.
Your friends seem to be having
a lot of fun in the pool.
I'm actually a recent
transplant in this worl-
I mean, this city.
I haven't made any friends yet,
so I'm a little jealous.
Oh yeah?
We finished exercising for 30 minutes!
Nice job!
I'm really feeling it in my legs!
And with proper nutrition,
you can double the effect!
All it takes is some vegetables
and high-quality protein...
Elves only eat vegetables.
But that's just a preference, right?
Thigh and tenderloin
meat is the best!!
I recommend you try meat.
Specifically pork, which is rich
in vitamins and carnitine.
Don't you dare!
Eating pigs is beyond cruel!
Whoa. Those ears...
Sneaky! I didn't realize because of
how slimmed down she is,
but this girl is an Orc!
"Orc"?
A race of creatures that live in
the forest just like us elves.
Their bodies tend to be very stout.
To put it simply...
They're piglike humanoids.
No, we are not!
I mean, I guess we do share
a slight bond with pigs!
Slight?
A legend passed down among Orcs, you say?
Yes. It speaks of a technique in this world
that even Orcs can use to lose weight.
So I came here and discovered
the ancient art of the "diet"!
It taught me that pool exercise was best
for people with hefty bodies like me.
And after giving it a try,
I found it was very effective!
Once I learn all the diet techniques
and return home,
then Orcs will never get made fun of
for being "fatheads" or "slowpokes"!
You could learn a thing or two from her.
Well, if an Orc can lose this much weight,
then you weren't kidding about
how effective swimming is.
Yeah, I've never seen an Orc
this in shape before.
R-really?
Not bad for an inferior Orc.
Well, shucks!
They're making fun of her.
Swimming really is the better exercise, huh?
I think I'll give it a try.
Why not save it for another day?
My legs feel like jelly,
so there's no way I can swim.
Less jelly and more flab, in your case!
What did you say?!
Death to dark elves!
You first, fatty!
You're more of a pig than the Orcs!
Stop! It's dangerous to
roughhouse by the pool!
Are you okay?!
I'm s-s-s-s-s-sorry!
I'm such a good swimmer!
Nothing like a popsicle after a good swim.
Indeed!
Really warms ya up!
Wait, that's backwards!
Massage Relaxation
Beauty - Health - Diet
How's it going?
Have you been swimming every day?
Nah... only once in a while
is enough for me.
Aw, jeez.
Oh, welcome in.
Mister Human!
Oku?!
What on Earth happened to you?!
They shut down the pool
at the gym for renovations!
And it caused my weight to bounce back!
What am I gonna do?!
Well...
Don't fret. It'll be okay.
Let's turn that frown upside down
by eating some French fries.
Oink! But I'm trying to lose weight!
Please! Teach me other ways
that I can shed some pounds!